<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Modern Jihad</title>
    <link>https://jihad.icu/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Modern Jihad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; fearness.org 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 21:37:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jihad.icu/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Prelim Phase</title>
      <link>https://jihad.icu/post/prelim-phase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 21:37:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jihad.icu/post/prelim-phase/</guid>
      <description>I must run simulations and cost / effect ratios on the most efficient method available to me. I am running on a tight budget. Until I can promo the idea more at least and find a sponsor I&amp;rsquo;ll need the best ROI I can get.
I believe in open source so I want to document some of the interesting, hard and not well documented domestic terrorism tactics. I wont hold back on technical details so if you aren&amp;rsquo;t into the inner workings this may not be for you, if you are into that, then welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Suggestions for June 12th 2018</title>
      <link>https://jihad.icu/post/introduction-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 14:50:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jihad.icu/post/introduction-books/</guid>
      <description>I think what got me interested in the possibilities of bioweapons in the first place was reading the book Biohazard: The Chilling True Story of the Largest Covert Biological Weapons Program in the World&amp;ndash;Told from the Inside by the Man Who Ran It by Ken Alibek. That lead me to study to other facilities such as Lab 257 by Michael C. Carroll.
Then who could forget about outbreaks of dangerous viruses such as Ebola or Marburg?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck Everyones World</title>
      <link>https://jihad.icu/post/fuck-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 23:43:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jihad.icu/post/fuck-everyone/</guid>
      <description>I just got out of the hospital after weeks of being switched around on medications. None of them really help all they do is make it hard to concentrate and make me forget things and they take away my ability to tell the future, which I need to keep no matter what.
That&amp;rsquo;s why I stopped taking my meds as soon as I got out of the hospital. I was clever and filled my script, that way they will think I&amp;rsquo;m taking it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>